{
  "decks": {
    "0": "Все",
    "1": "Математика",
    "2":  "Столицы"
  },
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 0,
      "deck": [ "0", "1" ],
      "question": "2+2",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "deck": [ "0", "1" ],
      "question": "2+3",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "deck": [ "0", "1" ],
      "question": "2+4",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "deck": [ "0" ],
      "question": "2+5",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "deck": [ "0" ],
      "question": "2+6",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "deck": [ "0" ],
      "question": "2+7",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "deck": [ "0" ],
      "question": "2+8",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "deck": [ "0", "2" ],
      "question": "Столица Российской Федерации",
      "answer": "Москва"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "deck": [ "0", "2" ],
      "question": "Столица Японии",
      "answer": "Токио"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "deck": [ "0", "2" ],
      "question": "Столица Китая",
      "answer": "Пекин"
    }
  ]
}